Hey, what kind of a man keeps my head like a radish, those eyes like
onions, your stomach like a goose, I beat you every
day, my head is like a sane man, I will
break your neck, my stomach has become an enemy, it has
become an enemy [laughter]
Come on, tell me, what do you say? Sometimes a man and a
sheikh are sown, sometimes they become brothers, sometimes they
become enemies again, so
where are we enemies now? Right now,
you are my sheikh and I am your man,
yes, yes, if you go to
practice fighting, then only then will
we become enemies,
yes, today, I will eat the sev and
throw everyone away.  [Laughter]
But what power does it have to eat Sev Mamra?  Uncle
looks powerful.
Hey, okay.  He
did it badly, my man reminded me, Chanya
Khan wants to throw everyone away [laughter], I
left this,
this is the problem,
I am a fool, today we have to change the team, my
job is
you come to our team and
send the teammate to Bakulbhai's team,
no, no, Mamrabhai, believe me a little,
but send Mamrabhai to that team and
you come to our team too, Mamrabhai is the
captain, don't believe me,
yes, I laugh, then even if the team is like this, yes, yes, if I take it, then
this will happen or not, I will see
[laughter]
Now, I have to eat rice every day, so I will get strength,
all those people will see it and I will see a goat, then the
innocent grandfather will laugh and say, "
Hey, this is me, that's Sana,
Sana, I am the job, father,
you said to boil Sana, oh father
[laughter]
Otherwise, you didn't say to boil Sana, you said to boil Chana, you said to
boil Chhana.  You didn't say anything,
you only said to boil the ghee,
but I had eaten the gram, so you must have
understood that.
Hey, tell me, you said to boil the gram,
but what's the use of boiling the gram? Tell
me, you have to eat boiled gram, believe me, even if you do
n't eat the gram,
start practicing tying. The more you
practice, the more we benefit,
yes, I laugh, then
first you beat me,
you will beat me slowly like this,
yes [laughter]
Father [shouting]
Oh father, I will also beat your ghee, I did
n't beat you, Mamrabhai beat you,
so
maybe Mamrabhai came in front of you, I will
beat you a little slowly,
yes, I laugh, now you beat me, oh father,
why did I beat you with a stretch, I did
n't beat you, I ate the ghee, I beat you
[laughter] I'm lost,
oh father, oh father, I beat
you
Father [shouting]
Bakula beat me,
father, oh father,
Mamrabhai beat you again,
this Bakula brother has come,
I have reached the limit,
why do you know that yesterday Samakbhai beat you
.  Now, Samakbhai's drum sounds so little that it
hurts his teeth, but if he plays the drum, it will hurt
him.
[Laughter] Laughter.
What if Bakulbhai, you
told Samakbhai that you don't hurt my teeth, then
why did Samakbhai play the drum when his teeth hurt?
Now, he is left-handed, so he plays the drum with his left hand.
Samakbhai is not left-handed, he is right-handed.  Yes,
I said,
even if you don't say that, then
our team won't lose, then there's
no need to tell anyone's sore nerve.
Now let's leave that matter alone. Let's go practice. If
Samakbhai comes in front of me, then I have to throw him out.
Today, I will send Samakbhai in front of you. If you are a
traitor like that, then you will
lose.
One thing, O father, O father, Samak [laughter]
O father, [shouting] O father, father, man
[laughter] Oh, grandfather,
Mamarabhai [shouting] O father, O
father, Bakudo,
O father, O [shouting] Father, I do
n't want to stop practicing. [laughter] So, just a
little while, you practice tying alone.
Even if you come on time, you will have to
pay the fine. [laughter]
Why do
you practice alone?
We all have to practice a little while, but
we  Fill in the blanks of where you ate something.
Hey uncle, it seems like you have made a plan, if the soaked
sana falls and the sev falls, oh
[clears throat] Bapa, he
said about the hemp baba, you are a
wise baba,
but that talk is over now, now
I am
not going to talk about me anymore, now I am going to waste it in practice, that loser, hello
[music]
Vikambhai, Samakbhai, come and
say, Ivda, it has been sitting since then, hey
Mamrabhai, I applied it, or else I applied
turmeric, it will hurt, no, it will hurt, and
then I have to apply turmeric,
this is me, innocent grandfather, if I give you turmeric, if it hurts, then no, yes,
say it with a smile [laughter]
Hello, then practice should continue, should I form a new team
or keep this team,
new team, I will start work, from where I
stopped practice yesterday,
this time our team will be on the other side
.   If you do
n't mind, I'll beat the innocent grandfather a drum
.  I have yet to beat the drum.   Hello
brother, hello
Tikambhai, get
ready to eat the drum,
father, father,
I have won,
wow, man, wow, why did the drum beat Bhola Dada
and
yes, [laughter]
Bhola Dada, you came after eating the drum, so
now who will come from your team,
Tikambhai, I am coming, Makulbhai, you will beat me,
yes, I Tikambhai, I will beat you, and if you beat me,
then
my drum [laughter]
Why,
oh Bakuda, you beat Chikamba,
yes, it happened to
me, you clapped
[laughter] No, no, I beat Chikamba's hand
and Chikamba beat my hand, I did
n't beat him, I clapped
[laughter]
Bakulbhai, you got one point,
we got one point.  Sambakbhai defeated me, Bhola
Dada's man defeated Bhola Dada, and if a
match is tried between you and Tikambhai, then
arrange another round, but this time
not with a drum, but with a single blow.
Which one of you will come out on top?   If
I come,
Bakuda will let me go.
Go away,
you have come back to oppose me.
Yes [screams]
so get ready to get [ __ ].  Hey
where did the snow fall? [Screaming] Oh father [Laughter]
Look, you cheated and pushed me.
Why did you cheat and push me? Yes, you cheated and
your money fell. [
Screaming] Do that. You cheated me.
I [Laughter] Laughter. When did your money fall?
Take it.
You take it.
I don't see the money. So you cheated me.
[Laughter] Now I cheated
you. Go away. Oh father. Oh father. Oh father. Oh father. Oh father. Oh father. Oh father.
Oh father.
Oh father. You left. Oh father. Even if you cheated me,
I went to work on that team. So you cheated and pushed
me. So that's why you
left. No
problem. I'll take revenge now. Just
say it's okay. Who will come from your team?
I'm coming.
I'm coming from our team.
Bakulbhai, you agree. Send the brother.  You
go, no
problem,
Tikambhai. The barrier is going to be closed.  Right now,
Mamrabhai will give Bakulbhai a push and he will make a
pile.  Yes, the
clouds are about to gather. Now Bakudo will push me
and it will knock out Mamrabhai's teeth.
Yes, [laughter]
Hey Bakulbhai, you will push me.
Yes, I will push you and you push me.
No problem.
[laughter]
I, Mamrabhai, you and I thought that if you push
Bakulbhai, Bakulbhai will be in a heap. You have pushed me.
Where did you push me? You must have met Bakulbhai and
came back. It felt like that. No,
Bakulbhai pushed me in my hand.
I pushed Bakulbhai in his hand. So
who is coming from your team?
Tikambhai comes from our team.  I don't mind if
a peer from our team comes,
go, Tikambhai, let's
have tea,
okay? [laughter] You push me in my direction
and I push you in my direction. I don't mind
[laughter]
Why did Sam push me? There was no sound.
Even if there was no sound, Tikambhai felt the push.
If you say so, who wins and who loses in this? It's not the same. The
second round is over. Who won?
We won that.
You are ours, we won.
You didn't win it, and we didn't win it either.
Hey, we'll have to hold one more round.
So this time, one by one, beat the drum or the drumstick
.   If there's
any problem, go ahead and
bring a trick, Samakbhai. [Laughter]
You see, this time we'll win right away.  If you go,
Tikambhai, if you are being deceived, then what's the
problem, Mamrabhai, don't be shy this time, deceive that,
Chamkbhai, come and take a rag,
but I will ask for work,
you will find out now, you deceiver,
I have asked for so many jobs, is that
deception strong or not, you will have to know, don't be afraid of
that deception,
yes,
I will deceive you, which one will hurt
more, and who will win? [laughter] Oh
father, father, father, father, father, father, father, father, father, father, father,
father,
which one will hurt more,
all those deceptions have been made, so what's the
problem, this time I will go first,
that loser,
I am coming, then I am
coming, Mamrabhai,
I will go in front of Bakulbhai, you will find out now, if you are being deceived, you will find out now
.  [Laughter] So, are
you going to beat me or should I beat you
?
You beat me up.
Oh father, oh father [screaming]
[laughter]
Now you beat me.  That's Haru
[bell]
[laughter]
Hey
hey what happened to me?  When I hit Bakulbhai's
head, a thud sounded
.
Hey, Bakulbhai must have built something in Waha.
Hey, uncle,
who will come from your team now?
I'll
tie a rope for you
[laughter]
Now you won't be fooled, you
loser,
look, Bakulbhai tied a rope in the Doha canal
.  No matter what the problem is,
I'll go and beat you up with a broom.
Hello innocent grandfather, first you beat me,
then I'll beat you.
No problem,
Arr [screaming]
Now I'll beat you up.
That loser [laughter]
Oh father, oh father, you're sitting there, you need to
hit your feet a little.  So you sit down, wow, you've already
tied the knot,
you know,
yes, yes,
who won,
who's that? So, we'll have to hold
one more round
[laughter]
Oh, father, how
many rounds are there now?
You all go and beat me, you're going to
eat my innocent grandfather.
You two are so stupid. You need to practice a little bit to tie, you do
n't have to tie at all, that's a laugh
[laughter]